{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471648394","data":{"timestamp":" 947471648394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mukhwana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUKHWANA"," userResponse":" MUKHWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471649454","data":{"timestamp":" 947471649454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mukhwana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUKHWANA"," userResponse":" MUKHWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471652305","data":{"timestamp":" 947471652305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471653369","data":{"timestamp":" 947471653368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471657341","data":{"timestamp":" 947471657340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWANA"," userResponse":" START_HAWANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471658457","data":{"timestamp":" 947471658457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWANA"," userResponse":" HAWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471659513","data":{"timestamp":" 947471659512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWANA"," userResponse":" HAWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471667078","data":{"timestamp":" 947471667077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipomwona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471668151","data":{"timestamp":" 947471668150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alipomwona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWONA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471672633","data":{"timestamp":" 947471672632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutokana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" KUTOKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471673701","data":{"timestamp":" 947471673701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutokana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKANA"," userResponse":" KUTOKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471678527","data":{"timestamp":" 947471678527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINA"," userResponse":" SHINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471679590","data":{"timestamp":" 947471679589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINA"," userResponse":" SHINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471686146","data":{"timestamp":" 947471686146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuvuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUNA"," userResponse":" KUVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471687212","data":{"timestamp":" 947471687212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuvuna"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUNA"," userResponse":" KUVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471693333","data":{"timestamp":" 947471693332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471694405","data":{"timestamp":" 947471694405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waliona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471699736","data":{"timestamp":" 947471699735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITANA"," userResponse":" START_ALIITANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471706847","data":{"timestamp":" 947471706847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITANA"," userResponse":" ALIITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471707904","data":{"timestamp":" 947471707904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" aliitana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITANA"," userResponse":" ALIITANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471712076","data":{"timestamp":" 947471712076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471713134","data":{"timestamp":" 947471713134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.na.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471717009","data":{"timestamp":" 947471717008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471717128","data":{"timestamp":" 947471717128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" c7d2ae82-6734-4875-bbbf-651536f8c8a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.na.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msichana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471759496","data":{"timestamp":" 947471759495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471761967","data":{"timestamp":" 947471761967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471770522","data":{"timestamp":" 947471770522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471772612","data":{"timestamp":" 947471772612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471780969","data":{"timestamp":" 947471780969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471790204","data":{"timestamp":" 947471790203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471793007","data":{"timestamp":" 947471793007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471803381","data":{"timestamp":" 947471803381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471805014","data":{"timestamp":" 947471805014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471813178","data":{"timestamp":" 947471813178"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" )"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471819891","data":{"timestamp":" 947471819891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471825762","data":{"timestamp":" 947471825761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471827430","data":{"timestamp":" 947471827429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471839211","data":{"timestamp":" 947471839211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471848847","data":{"timestamp":" 947471848847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471856283","data":{"timestamp":" 947471856282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" )"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471863925","data":{"timestamp":" 947471863925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471866546","data":{"timestamp":" 947471866546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471884288","data":{"timestamp":" 947471884288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471886242","data":{"timestamp":" 947471886242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471894732","data":{"timestamp":" 947471894732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471896331","data":{"timestamp":" 947471896331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471912571","data":{"timestamp":" 947471912571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471919308","data":{"timestamp":" 947471919308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471927362","data":{"timestamp":" 947471927362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471934811","data":{"timestamp":" 947471934811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471941388","data":{"timestamp":" 947471941388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471953270","data":{"timestamp":" 947471953270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471956279","data":{"timestamp":" 947471956279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471966800","data":{"timestamp":" 947471966799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471974040","data":{"timestamp":" 947471974039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471982157","data":{"timestamp":" 947471982157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471984348","data":{"timestamp":" 947471984348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947471999212","data":{"timestamp":" 947471999211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 41df021d-2082-4e74-a979-dd1fdaf88e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472026647","data":{"timestamp":" 947472026647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472033377","data":{"timestamp":" 947472033377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472041256","data":{"timestamp":" 947472041255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472044078","data":{"timestamp":" 947472044078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472061310","data":{"timestamp":" 947472061310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472069914","data":{"timestamp":" 947472069914"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472072033","data":{"timestamp":" 947472072033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472083110","data":{"timestamp":" 947472083110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472099431","data":{"timestamp":" 947472099431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472106555","data":{"timestamp":" 947472106555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472108629","data":{"timestamp":" 947472108629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472118777","data":{"timestamp":" 947472118777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472125537","data":{"timestamp":" 947472125537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472128030","data":{"timestamp":" 947472128030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472141153","data":{"timestamp":" 947472141153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472143252","data":{"timestamp":" 947472143252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472151000","data":{"timestamp":" 947472151000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472158161","data":{"timestamp":" 947472158161"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472160149","data":{"timestamp":" 947472160149"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472168169","data":{"timestamp":" 947472168169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472179348","data":{"timestamp":" 947472179348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472181779","data":{"timestamp":" 947472181779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472190252","data":{"timestamp":" 947472190252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472197019","data":{"timestamp":" 947472197018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472198892","data":{"timestamp":" 947472198892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472209281","data":{"timestamp":" 947472209281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472211314","data":{"timestamp":" 947472211314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472219300","data":{"timestamp":" 947472219299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472226599","data":{"timestamp":" 947472226599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472229670","data":{"timestamp":" 947472229670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.na.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472244611","data":{"timestamp":" 947472244609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 026de0cb-42b2-4cdd-bc48-f926ee6ff6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.na.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write___na"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472276713","data":{"timestamp":" 947472276713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 598c7ed1-deea-49d3-b8e5-0705bb572961"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472277336","data":{"timestamp":" 947472277336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 598c7ed1-deea-49d3-b8e5-0705bb572961"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472277593","data":{"timestamp":" 947472277592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 598c7ed1-deea-49d3-b8e5-0705bb572961"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472278163","data":{"timestamp":" 947472278162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 598c7ed1-deea-49d3-b8e5-0705bb572961"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472279307","data":{"timestamp":" 947472279307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 598c7ed1-deea-49d3-b8e5-0705bb572961"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472279930","data":{"timestamp":" 947472279930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 598c7ed1-deea-49d3-b8e5-0705bb572961"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472280026","data":{"timestamp":" 947472280026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 598c7ed1-deea-49d3-b8e5-0705bb572961"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472298608","data":{"timestamp":" 947472298607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwishoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHONI"," userResponse":" MWISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472301902","data":{"timestamp":" 947472301901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472305264","data":{"timestamp":" 947472305264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANI"," userResponse":" TANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472308410","data":{"timestamp":" 947472308409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwilini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILINI"," userResponse":" MWILINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472311688","data":{"timestamp":" 947472311687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pini"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472314823","data":{"timestamp":" 947472314822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jioni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472317997","data":{"timestamp":" 947472317996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichakani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472321531","data":{"timestamp":" 947472321531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" malishoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALISHONI"," userResponse":" MALISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472325135","data":{"timestamp":" 947472325134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" juani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472328281","data":{"timestamp":" 947472328281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mgeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ni.rand.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472331800","data":{"timestamp":" 947472331799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mgeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472331868","data":{"timestamp":" 947472331868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" 3aa3fcf4-2af5-4d2b-8f58-14f404f89039"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ni.rand.14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mgeni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGENI"," userResponse":" MGENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472355822","data":{"timestamp":" 947472355822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lini_mali-taya-lini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lini"," userResponse":" lini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472366376","data":{"timestamp":" 947472366376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_hawa-ziwa-tani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472377017","data":{"timestamp":" 947472377017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_titi-bata-uani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472386935","data":{"timestamp":" 947472386935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pini_kaka-bado-pini"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pini"," userResponse":" pini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472395438","data":{"timestamp":" 947472395437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_tani-wawe-koti"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472404905","data":{"timestamp":" 947472404905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_kuni-pili-mali"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuni"," userResponse":" kuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472413663","data":{"timestamp":" 947472413663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_honi_duma-honi-hewa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" honi"," userResponse":" honi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472422883","data":{"timestamp":" 947472422882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_uani-yote-tuna"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472431695","data":{"timestamp":" 947472431695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_ruka-kata-nini"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472440990","data":{"timestamp":" 947472440990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" uani"," userResponse":" uani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947472446766","data":{"timestamp":" 947472446765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_053353"," gameId":" e44f0ebc-55bc-4b8d-8cd3-d671764dde54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.show.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_uani_raha-uani-tisa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}